(Leonard:)And then,
instead of living alone
(Raj:)in my tiny apartment,
I'd have a big mansion.
(Bernadette:)That sounds great.
(Raj:)It is.
(Raj:)If you like wandering
around a big, empty house
(Raj:)with no one to love you.
(Howard:)We'd come visit you.
No, you wouldn't.
(Raj:)You'd be intimidated
by my wealth and fame.
(Raj:)My only friends would be
(Raj:)my genetically engineered
monkey butler
(Raj:)and the little people I hired
to be my living chess set.
(Bernadette:)He's taking a turn to
the dark side, isn't he?
(Leonard:)Hold on.
He could come back.
(Raj:)Oh, what's the point
of everything?
(Howard:)Nope. He's gone.
(Raj:)You know it's been more
than a year
(Raj:)since I've even kissed a girl?
(Howard:)What about that hookup
at Comic-Con you told me about?
(Raj:)Oh, grow up. I was lying.
(Raj:)I lie all the time.
Nobody wants to kiss me.
(Bernadette:)Oh, you poor, poor thing.
(Bernadette:)Raj, you have to know
you're a wonderful man.
(Bernadette:)There are a lot of girls out
there who'll want to kiss you.
(Raj:)Where?
(Bernadette:)You just have to look.